<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">App_Turistico</string>
    <string name="desc_avenida_paulista">Paulista Avenue is considered one of the main financial centers of the city, as well as one of its most characteristic tourist spots, the avenue reveals its importance not only as an economic center, but also as a cultural and entertainment center, as well as hosting a large number of company headquarters, banks, consulates, hotels and hospitals.</string>
    <string name="desc_bairro_liberdade">Liberdade is a tourist district known as the largest stronghold of the Japanese community in the world outside the world. The neighborhood keeps a lot of Japanese and Oriental tradition through the typical festivals that take place throughout the year, such as: Chinese New Year, Hanamatsuri, Tanabata Matsuri, Toyo Matsuri, Moti Tsuki and others.</string>
    <string name="desc_beco_do_batman">Beco do Batman is a lane located in Vila Madalena, a bohemian neighborhood on the west side of the city of São Paulo. The passage got its name due to a graffiti of the eponymous character from DC Comics many years ago, and ended up becoming a tourist spot due to dozens of graffiti painted on its walls.</string>
    <string name="desc_centro_cultural_bnco_brsl">The Banco do Brasil São Paulo Cultural Center, also known as CCBB São Paulo, was inaugurated on April 21, 2001. The old building, built in 1901, was purchased in 1923 by Banco do Brasil, it was Banco do Brasil\'s first building Brazil in São Paulo.<br />The elements of the original architecture have been restored, thus maintaining the lines that make it one of the most significant examples of this city\'s early century architecture.</string>
    <string name="desc_estadio_morumbi">The Cícero Pompeu de Toledo Stadium, better known as Morumbi Stadium, is a stadium built to host soccer matches, being the official headquarters of the Brazilian soccer team São Paulo Futebol Clube, having already hosted the Brazilian team on several occasions. The stadium was designed to accommodate 150 thousand spectators, but, due to several renovations and the installation of cabins, its capacity was reduced to 72 039.</string>
    <string name="desc_marco_zero">Ground Zero of Praça da Sé is a geographical monument in front of the Sé Cathedral. The marble-covered hexagonal prism represents the geographic center of the city, where all the distance measurements located on its toponymic plates and the city are established. de São Paulo recognizes the monument as a strong feeling in São Paulo, emphasizing the role of formation not only in the State of São Paulo, but also in Brazil. Ground Zero is full of symbolic value.</string>
    <string name="desc_mercado_municipal">Mercado Municipal Paulistano, also known as Mercadão, is an important historical and architectural building in the city, the Mercado Municipal also stands out today as a cultural and tourist hub. The building underwent restoration in 2004, which included the construction of a mezzanine to house restaurants.</string>
    <string name="desc_mosteiro_de_sao_bento">The Monastery of São Bento is a historical and religious site. About 45 monks live in the Monastery, where they dedicate their lives to the tradition of \"pray and work\", the religious are always willing to receive guests and visitors, welcoming those who come looking for prayer, retreat, spiritual guidance or confession. they are always ready to receive guests and visitors, welcoming those who come looking for prayer, retreat, spiritual guidance or confession.</string>
    <string name="desc_masp">Museum of Art of São Paulo Assis Chateaubriand is one of the most important Brazilian cultural institutions. It was founded in 1947 and throughout its history, it has stood out for a series of important initiatives in the field of museology and artistic training, as well as for its strong didactic performance in addition to having the most important and comprehensive collection of Western art in the world. Latin America and the entire southern hemisphere, in which the consistent sets referring mainly to the Italian and French schools are notable.</string>
    <string name="desc_parque_ibirapuera">Ibirapuera Park is an urban park that in 2017 was the most visited park in Latin America, with approximately 14 million visits, in addition to being one of the most photographed places in the world.<br />The park has several attractions for the public, from cultural and educational tours such as guided walks, bird watching activities, with sculptures, museums and historical monuments, as well as gardens and landscapes full of flowers and trees.</string>
    <string name="desc_pateo_do_colegio">The Pátio do Colégio is an archaeological site, an apostolic work belonging to the Society of Jesus. Composed of the Anchieta Museum, the Manoel da Nóbrega Auditorium, the Tenerife Gallery, the Plaza Canarias and the Beato José de Anchieta Church. Daily Masses are celebrated in the Church at noon. On Sundays, mass is celebrated at 10:00 am.</string>
    <string name="desc_pico_jaragua">The Pico do Jaraguá is one of the highest points in the municipality of São Paulo and you can ascend to its summit by a paved road (Estrada Turística do Jaraguá) and by the Camino Pai Zé (1,450 meters long). When you reach the top, you have a view mainly of the western part of Greater São Paulo. The Mário Covas ring road can also be seen to the rear.</string>
    <string name="desc_pinacoteca">The Pinacoteca do Estado de São Paulo is one of the most important art museums in Brazil. After the reform in the 1990s, it became one of the most dynamic cultural institutions in the country, integrating itself into the international exhibition circuit, promoting diverse cultural events and maintaining an active bibliographic production.</string>
    <string name="desc_rua_25_de_marco">Rua 25 de Março is a public road located in the central region of the city of São Paulo considered as the largest commercial center in Latin America, as it consists of one of the busiest shopping centers for retailers and wholesalers in the city. Its origin is linked to important colonization and urbanization processes in the capital of São Paulo, being an important region for the city\'s history due to its commercial and social activities.</string>
    <string name="desc_solar_da_marqueza">The Solar da Marquesa de Santos, is the headquarters of the Museum of the City of São Paulo and several cultural varieties. The first references in documents to the Solar da Marquesa de Santos are dated from the period between 1739 and 1754 with different architectures, furniture and houses from that time.</string>
    <string name="desc_trilha_mata_atlantica">The Atlantic Forest Path is a Brazilian trail that crosses the Serra do Mar, whose predominant ecosystem is the Atlantic Forest. With more than 4 thousand km of extension, the trail will start in the Aparados da Serra National Park, in the north of Rio Grande do Sul, and will extend until the Desengano State Park, in the north of Rio de Janeiro.</string>
    <string name="search_text">Search Here</string>
    <string name="titulo_pnts_turstcos">Attractions of São Paulo</string>
    <string name="aviso_acesso_localizacao">This application requires the use of GPS to work correctly, would you like to allow it?</string>
    <string name="centro">Central Region</string>
    <string name="sul">South Region</string>
    <string name="suldoeste" translatable="false">Southwestern Region</string>
    <string name="oeste">Region West</string>
</resources>